Newland/Zeuner Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music of Charles Zeuner (Box 48-57)
  - Instruction and study materials (Box 56)
    - [Miscellaneous cover pages, fragments and scraps] (Box 56)
51 • First Organ Concerto
48 • Fuga für die Orgel
49 • Fugues
49 • Gallops
57 • Gloria to a Jubilate Deo by B. Carr
57 • Good Night
51 • Governor Everett's Quickstep
48 • Great fantasia
51 • Hope, our Support
51 • Hushed is the voice of Judah's mirth
55 • If thou hast crush'd a flow'r
49 • Introduction and Variations to Hail Columbia
57 • Let other nations proudly tell
54 • Make a joyful noise
49 • Marches
51 • Masonic March
57 • Military March, full Band
52 • Missa (No. III in E-flat)
54 • Missa No. 3 in E-flat
52 • Missa No. 3 in E-flat Organ accompaniment by William Newland
55 • Mrs. Adams Welcome to General Jackson
54 • O all ye Nations
52 • O all ye nations praise the Lord
52 • O cease my wandering soul
52 • O happy is the man
52 • O praise God in his holiness
52 • O praise ye the Lord
54 • O Salutaris hostia (from the 1st Organ Concerto, vocal melody by W. A. Newland)
51 • Organ accompaniment by William Newland
50 • Organ Concerto (No. 2)
50 • Organ Concerto [No. 1]
50 • Organ Concerto [No. 1]
48 • Organ fantasia
48 • Organ fantasia and Capriccio
52 • Parting hymn
48 • Polonaises
48 • Polonaises
50 • Pot Pourri für Posthorn
52 • Praise ye Jehovah's name
54 • Praise ye the Lord
54 • Praise ye the Lord
57 • Praise Ye the Lord, fourth [of] July Cantata 1838 [in D]
49 • President Harrison's Funeral March
49 • Quicksteps
57 • Quicksteps
52 • Rejoice in the Lord O ye righteous
51 • Rondo Polacca
51 • Rondo Polacca pour le Cor in Es
49 • Rondos [and] Rondinos
55 • Sechs Lieder von Theodor Körner
51 • Second Grand Concerto for the Organ
50 • Solo für Violino
49 • Sonata
57 • Spanish Dance No. 4
55 • Take, oh take those lips away
57 • Te Deum
55 • The Bride's Farewell
53 • The Feast of Tabernacles
53 • The Feast of Tabernacles, an Oratorio, in two parts. Morning and Evening Sacrifice. The Words by Rev. Henry Ware, of Cambridge, the Music by Ch. Zeuner.
55 • The Glasses Sparkling on the Bord
52 • The Lord unto my Lord thus spake
52 • The swift declining day
57 • The Thunderstorm
54 • The Thunderstorm
49 • Themes and Variations
52 • There is an hour of peaceful rest
54 • There is an hour of peaceful rest
55 • These prairies glow with flowers
49 • Three Divertisments for the Piano Forte [on] subjects from Norma by Ch. Zeuner.
51 • Two Organ Concertos, Nos. I & II.
51 • Variations on [Home] Sweet Home
49 • Variations on the American National Song: Yankee Doodle
49 • VI Variationen für das Pianoforte
55 • Wallhaide
49 • Waltzes
54 • We praise thee, O God
55 • When that I was a little tiny boy
55 • Wiegenlied
48 • Zeuner's Organ Voluntaries in two parts.
50 • zum Coda
Zeuner, Charles (arranger)
55 • Break my heart! Break my heart!
55 • The Evening gun
55 • The Sailor's grave
55 • Wandering by the moonlight shore
51 • Washington's March
Zimmer
29 • Mass No. 2 in B-flat.
29 • Missa Brevis
Zingarelli, Nicolo
38 • Fuga a 4 di Nicolo Zingarelli.(Beilage zur allgem. musikalischen Zeitung.1821. No. 52; No. V).
32 • Laudate pueri Dominum
43 • Lucido eccelso Nume
Zumsteeg, Johann Rudolf
43 • An die Menschengelichter
43 • Canzonette